Fact_Ratings- This fact table contains the references to the dimension tables and three facts: "appalling" which contains the count of titles that have an average rating score of 2.0 or below, "average" which contains the count of titles that have an average rating score of 2.1 to 7.9, and "outstanding" which contains the count of title that have an average rating score of 8.0 or above. The references to the dimension tables, start_year which references the Dim_Year table, genre which references the Dim_Genre table, and title_type which references the Dim_Title_Type table, are foreign keys and they also make the composite primary key for this fact table. 

Dim_Year- This is a year dimension table with only one field, "start_year". This dimension table is like a master list that contains unique values of year. Since start_year is a primary key, it is unique and not null.

Dim_Genre- This is a genre dimension table with only one field, "genre". genre is a primary key, and it is unique and not null. It is like a master list that consist of unique genres.

Dim_Title_Type- This is a title type dimension table with only one field, "title_type". The table contains unique title types. title_type is the primary key for this table, hence it is unique and not null.